imyanmarads.com 2014-02-13

# Privacy Policy ::: iMyanmarAds.com - Brought to You by iMyanmar

This Privacy Policy is effective as of 1st March 2013.

iMyanmarAds.com (“iMyanmarAds”) is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains the data collection and use practices of iMyanmarAds and all related websites owned or registered to iMyanmarAds. It does not apply to any third party websites, applications, products or services for which iMyanmarAds is not responsible.

By accessing this site, you are consenting to the information collection and usage practices described in this policy as well as the site's Terms of Services. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY OR THE TERMS OF SERVICES PROVIDED ON THIS SITE, PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE ANY INFORMATION TO iMyanmarAds OR USE ANY OF THE SERVICES OR PRODUCTS OFFERED OR PROVIDED ON ANY OF THE WEBSITES REFERRED TO IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY. 

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy changes from time to time, and changes are effective upon posting on this page. It is your sole responsibility to periodically review this policy for updates, and you are solely responsible to be aware of any changes to this and all posted policies on this website. iMyanmarAds does not provide notices of any changes in any manner other than by posting the changes on this website.

**Information Collection, Use, and Dissemination practices**

This policy applies to iMyanmarAds's collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by iMyanmarAds on its, (a) websites, including all its divisions, subsidiaries and related companies (collectively, the "Websites"), (b) on various third party websites, and (c) other information collection, including the purchase of customer lists from third parties, or the use of customer lists from third parties. iMyanmarAds is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices of third party websites or applications.

**1\. Collection of Information**

**1.1. User Direct Information**

Each time you provide information to register your information, take advantage of a promotional offer, send us an email, or otherwise transmit information via the site, iMyanmarAds may obtain and collect personally identifiable information provided by you, including, but not limited to, your name, email address, mailing address, and telephone number. You may also provide us with information that, when combined with personally identifiable information, provides us with a better idea of who you are, including but not limited to your gender, birthday, marital status, and education level (collectively referred to as "personal information"). If you choose to access our website, use our services or purchase our products, we may require you to provide personal information as indicated on the forms throughout the site. You are not obligated to provide us with any information which you do not wish to share. 

**1.2. Registration Information  
**  
iMyanmarAds collects information from you when you voluntarily complete a iMyanmarAds registration page, order form, or survey either online by using the internet, offline by providing this information through the mail, in person or using a telephone. This information may be collected by registration pages, order forms, or surveys operated by third parties. This method of collection is collectively known as a "Registration." iMyanmarAds may also collect such information concerning you from another source and uses that information in combination with information provided from this website. Completing the Registration is completely voluntary, and you are under no obligation to provide Survey Information to iMyanmarAds or a third party, but you may receive incentives from iMyanmarAds or a third party in exchange for providing such information.

**1.3. Third Party List Information**

iMyanmarAds may collect information from you when you provide information to a third party and iMyanmarAds subsequently purchases, licenses, or otherwise acquires the information from the third party. Such purchased information may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, street address, zip/postal code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, industry of employment, personal and online interests, and such other information as the individual may have provided to the third party. When acquiring this information, iMyanmarAds seeks assurances from the third party that it has a right to transfer the information to iMyanmarAds and that the third party has a right to provide offers from advertisers to you included on the third party list.

**1.4. Other Methods of Collecting Personal Information  
**  
Other occasions when iMyanmarAds obtains information from you include (1) your claiming a prize or seeking to redeem an incentive offered by iMyanmarAds or by a third party, (2) your requests for assistance through iMyanmarAds's customer service, and (3) when you voluntarily subscribe to a iMyanmarAds service or newsletter.

**1.5. Cookies, Web Beacons, and Other Info Collected Using Technology  
**  
iMyanmarAds currently uses cookie and web beacon technology to associate certain Internet-related information about you with information about you in its database. Additionally, iMyanmarAds may use other new and evolving sources of information in the future.

(a) Cookies

"Cookies" are a feature on your browser software. If enabled, we may write cookies that may store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to any of the pages of this Site. Cookies assist us in tracking which of our features appeal the most to you and what content you may have viewed on past visits. When you visit this site again, cookies can enable us to customize our content according to your preferences. We may use cookies to: keep track of the number of return visits to this site; accumulate and report aggregate, statistical information on website usage; deliver specific content to you based on your interests or past viewing history; save your password for ease of access to our Site. You can disable cookies, although the Site may not function properly for you. Your browser preferences can be modified to accept or reject all cookies, or request a notification when a cookie is set. You may read more about cookies at http://cookiecentral.com. In order to use all of the features and functionality of iMyanmarAds's websites, you need to accept cookies.

(b) Web Beacons

A web beacon is a programming code that can be used to display an image on a web page, but can also be used to transfer your unique user identification to a database and associate you with previously acquired information about an individual in a database. This allows iMyanmarAds to track certain websites you visit. Web beacons are used to track online behavioral habits for marketing purposes to determine products or services you may be interested in. 

(c) IP Addresses

iMyanmarAds automatically tracks certain information based upon your behavior on the site. We may use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve you and our community. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on the site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on the site or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address. Your Internet Protocol ("IP") is a unique Internet "address" which is assigned to you by your Internet Service Provider ("ISP"). For local area network ("LAN"), DSL, or cable modem users, an IP address may be permanently assigned to a particular computer. IP addresses are automatically logged by Web servers, collecting information about a user's traffic patterns. While the IP address does not identify an individual by name, it may, with the cooperation of the ISP, be used to locate and identify an individual using the Web. Your IP address can, however, reveal what geographic area you are connecting from, or which ISP you are using. Finally, other websites you visit have IP addresses, and we may collect the IP addresses of those websites and their pages.

(d) Computer Profiles

iMyanmarAds may also collect and accumulate other anonymous data which will help us understand and analyze the Internet experience of our visitors. For instance, iMyanmarAds may accumulate visitor data relating to referring domain names, the type of browsers used, operating system software, screen resolutions, color capabilities, browser plug-ins, language settings, cookie preferences, search engine keywords and JavaScript enablement. When you provide us with Personal Identification Information, we are able to use such visitor data to identify you. 

(e) New Technology

The use of technology on the Internet, including cookies and web beacons, is rapidly developing. As a result, iMyanmarAds strongly encourages individuals to revisit this policy for any updates regarding its use of new technology.

**1.6. No Information Collected from Users under 13 Years of Age  
**  
iMyanmarAds requires its registrants be 13 years of age or above. iMyanmarAds will never knowingly collect any personal information about users under the age of 13. If iMyanmarAds obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from its database. Because it does not collect such information, iMyanmarAds has no such information to use or to disclose to third parties. 

**2\. Use of Individual Information  
**  
The following section describes how iMyanmarAds uses personal information. The uses described in these sections may change at any time. iMyanmarAds may also broaden its use of your personal information. iMyanmarAds may also use your personal information to provide commercial promotional offers to individuals or entities through, among other things, email advertising, telephone marketing, direct mail marketing, banner advertising and package stuffers.

**2.1. Discretion to Use Information  
**  
The personal information collected on this site and by third parties will be used to operate the site and to provide the services or products or carry out the transactions you have requested or authorized. iMyanmarAds may change or broaden its use of your personal information at any time. iMyanmarAds may use your personal information to provide promotional offers to individuals by means of email advertising, telephone marketing, direct mail marketing, online banner advertising, and package stuffers, and other possible uses.

iMyanmarAds MAY SELL OR TRANSFER INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE IN ITS SOLE DISCRETION. 

**2.2. Email  
**  
iMyanmarAds uses your personal information to provide promotional offers by email to you. iMyanmarAds may maintain separate email lists for different purposes. Because iMyanmarAds only sends emails when you have agreed to receive emails from iMyanmarAds or you have agreed to receive emails from third parties, statutes requiring certain formatting for unsolicited email are not applicable to email messages sent by iMyanmarAds.

**2.3. Profiling and Target Advertising**

iMyanmarAds uses your information to make and improve profiles of you and to track your online browsing habits and determine which areas of iMyanmarAds's websites are most frequently visited. This information helps iMyanmarAds to better understand your interests so that it can target advertising and promotions to you. iMyanmarAds may, at its discretion, target advertising by using email, direct mail, telephones, cell phones, and other means of communication to provide promotional offers.

**2.4. Storage of Personal Information  
**  
iMyanmarAds stores your information in a database on iMyanmarAds's servers. Our servers have security measures (provided by our hosting company) in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under iMyanmarAds's control. Notwithstanding such measures, iMyanmarAds cannot guarantee that its security measures will prevent iMyanmarAds computers from being illegally accessed, and your information from being stolen or altered. 

**3\. Use of Personal Information**

**3.1. Sale or Transfer to Third Parties  
**  
iMyanmarAds MAY SELL OR TRANSFER YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES FOR ANY PURPOSE IN iMyanmarAds'S SOLE DISCRETION. iMyanmarAds uses your personal information in the following 3 ways: 

1\. Customer Service; 

2\. Marketing; and 

3\. Complying with the law. 

**3.2. Customer Service  
**  
iMyanmarAds will use your personal information to respond to you, to process, validate and verify requests, to fulfill any of your requests and to tailor your experience on our websites. 

**3.3. Marketing**

iMyanmarAds will use your personal information for any marketing and survey purpose on behalf of iMyanmarAds and its affiliates and subsidiaries to send information to you about additional goods or services that may be of interest to you. In addition, iMyanmarAds will disclose your personal information to third party agents and independent contractors to help us conduct our marketing and survey efforts and to share with other companies in connection with marketing efforts including but not limited to direct marketing. You may have no relationship with these other companies. 

**3.4. Complying with Legal Process**

iMyanmarAds will use or disclose your personal information in response to subpoenas, court orders, warrants, or legal process, or to otherwise establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims or in the event you violate or breach an agreement with iMyanmarAds. iMyanmarAds will use and disclose your personal information if we believe you will harm the property or rights of iMyanmarAds, its owners, or those of iMyanmarAds's other customers. Finally, we will use or disclose your personal information if we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of iMyanmarAds's acceptable use policy, or as otherwise required by law when responding to subpoenas, court orders and other legal processes. 

**3.5. Order Fulfillment  
**  
iMyanmarAds will transfer your personal information to third parties when necessary to provide a product or service that you order from such third party while using iMyanmarAds's websites or when responding to offers provided by iMyanmarAds.

**3.6. Data Summary  
**  
iMyanmarAds may sell or transfer non-individualized information, such as summary or aggregated anonymous information about all persons or sub-groups of persons.

**4\. Privacy Practices of Third Parties  
**  
**4.1. Advertiser cookies and web beacons  
**  
Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies who place advertisements on the websites and on the internet generally may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other technology to collect information about individuals.
